# Andrew D. Choo

Cary, NC | (984)-789-7004 | AndyDChoo@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/AndyChoo | github.com/AndyDChoo | https://AndyChoo.herokuapp.com

## **Summary**

Full-Stack Web Developer with experience in collaborating on web applications. Teamwork, communication, and leadership have become my strong suits from 5+ years of part-time work. I have earned a full-stack web developer certification, and gained an immense amount of knowledge during and after my studies.

### **Technical Skills**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java

Web Technologies: Node.js, Git, Heroku

<u>Databases</u>: MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB

<u>Libraries</u>: React.js, Express.js, Material-UI, Bulma, Bootstrap, jQuery, Handlebars.js

## **Projects**

**RGMarket** | https://tinyurl.com/RetroGameMarket | HTML, CSS, JS, Bulma, Handlebars, node.js, express, MySQL, and Insomnia.

A Marketplace for users to purchase and sell their old and new video games.

- Styled and designed pages for the application to create a better experience for the users.
- Challenged to learn how to use Handlebars, Bulma, and Insomnia in one week.
- Implemented good naming conventions and comments to communicate with the backend devs.

**VodU** | <a href="https://vodu2.herokuapp.com/">https://vodu2.herokuapp.com/</a> | HTML, CSS, JS, React.js, Material UI, Express.js, Mongodb, and Node.js

An app for people to upload personal gaming clips for others to critique or make comments on.

- Styled and designed pages for the application to create a better experience for the users.
- Implemented reusable components to follow best practices to react application framework.
- Created a prototype for an upvoting system.

# **Experience**

Blu Water Ink - Calgary, Canada

2016 - Present

Business Manager

- Works in tandem with the owner to improve the company.
- Handled logistics for 1000+ sales a weekend.
- Calculated optimizations to boost revenue by over 50%.

#### Thai Spices and Sushi - Cary, NC

2016 - 2019

Server

- Served 80+ customers per night.
- Coordinated with a team of 2-4 other servers to provide excellent service.
- Responsible for opening and closing of the restaurant.

#### **Education**

Bootcamp Certificate - UNC, Chapel Hill

w Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Degree: UNC Charlotte, Charlotte, University City Blvd

August 2018 - May 2019

Completed 47 credit hours towards a B.S. in Computer Science.